Everything is subject to change.
كل شيء يتغير
You can do this.
يمكنك فعلها
Alright.
حسنا
I'll give it a shot.
سأحاول
Hello, hello.
مرحبا
Are you still in Capital City?
هل ما زلت في المدينة الرئيسية؟
Yeah.
لا
The meeting wraps up today.
انتهى الاجتماع اليوم
Does that mean you'll be free after that?
هل أنت حر
There's still a bit of wrap-up work.
لا يزال هناك بعض الأعمال
Once that's done, I'll head back to Yanping.
يمكننا العودة إلى يان بينغ بعد الانتهاء
Not thinking about staying in Capital City for a few more days?
ألا تفكر في البقاء في المدينة الرئيسية لبضعة أيام
I've got a ton of things waiting for me.
لا يزال هناك الكثير من الأشياء تنتظرها
And it's not that easy
علاوة على ذلك
for us to take time off.
ليس من السهل أن نطلب إجازة
We need to report to our superiors
يجب أن نطلب من القائد
and get official approval.
وافقت الشركة
You hardly
أنت
ever get a chance to go abroad.
ربما نادراً ما تخرج إلى الخارج
Now that you're out here fair and square,
أخيرا خرجت
why not take a few days off and relax?
لماذا لا تستغل هذه الفرصة للحصول على إجازة لبضعة أيام للاسترخاء
Talk to your boss.
اذهب وتحدث مع رئيسك
That's just the nature of my job.
طبيعة العمل هي هكذا
And I came with my colleagues.
بالإضافة إلى أن زملائي الذين أتوا معي
We are a team.
لقد جئنا معاً
I really messed things up
لقد تسببت لك
for you at work.
في العمل
At least give me a chance
يجب أن تفكر
to make it up to you.
أعطني فرصة للتعويض
Let me show you around Capital City.
سآخذك في المدينة
Why bring that up again?
لماذا تذكرين هذا؟
Didn't we agree to let it go?
ألم نترك الأمر؟
Just think about it.
فكر مرة أخرى
Alright.
هكذا
I'll send you my hotel address.
سأرسل لك عنواني
Once you're done on your end,
بعد الانتهاء من عملك
you can move over here.
يمكنك الانتقال إلى فندقي
I've got something to take care of now.
لدي بعض الأمور
Talk later. Bye.
أنا مشغول  مع السلامة
There's been a development.
الوضع الجديد الوضع الجديد
Yao Youzhi kept his word.
ياو يو جي لا يزال مخلصاً
His secretary just called
طلبت من سكرتيره أن يخبرني
to confirm a meeting with us
غدا الساعة الثانية بعد الظهر
tomorrow at 2 pm in his office.
لمقابلتنا في مكتبه
Great!
رائع
Mr. Yao, it's an honor to meet you.
سيد ياو، سررت بلقائك
We brought you a special gift from China.
لقد أحضرت لك خصيصاً في الصين
Cordyceps.
دونغ تشونغ شيا تشاو
Hope you'll like it.
أتمنى أن تعجبك
Lucy.
لو شي
Your father's turning 70 this year,
عيد ميلاد والدك سبعين هذا العام
right?
أليس كذلك
Cordyceps is really good for his health.
هذا دونغ تشونغ شيا تشاو يعامل والدك بشكل جيد
This is for him.
هذه الهدية لك
Thank you very much.
شكراً
Mr. Yao.
سيد ياو
I know there's been history between
أعلم أنك كنت مع رئيس شركتنا
you and our company president James.
كان جيمس هناك خلاف
But that was in the past.
هذا مشروع الماضي
We were simply doing our jobs,
الجميع يركز على أنفسهم
representing different interests.
ليس من أجل خلاف
It was never personal.
بل مصلحتهم الخاصة
I understand
اليوم
what you are here for.
أنا أعرف هدف لي دي
You have 5 minutes.
خمس دقائق
If you can't convince me by then,
لا يمكنك إقناعي في خمس دقائق
this is over.
انسي الأمر
I hope you understand.
آمل أن تفهم
When it comes to HTGR technologies,
التكنولوجيا الكهربائية والبرودة العالية
no PR firm knows more about it
لا يوجد شركة العلاقات العامة في العالم
than Leader Group.
أكثر دراية منا
And no PR firm enjoys as much trust
‫ولا توجد شركة العلاقات العامة‬
from Huaze Group as we do.
يمكن الحصول على ثقة هوا تسه
This partnership is about
‫هذه التعاون‬
mutual benefit.
من أجل مصالحنا المشتركة
I hope you'll give it serious consideration.
آمل أن نحصل على موافقتك
Huaze Group?
هوا تسه
Don't try to pressure me with Huaze Group.
‫لا تضغطي علي بهوا تسه
I can talk to them any time
‫يمكنني التواصل مع مجموعة هوا تسه في أي وقت
and have you replaced.
‫بدلاً منكم
But from a professional PR perspective...
لكن من وجهة نظر العلاقات العامة المهنية
I don't have time for a lecture.
ليس لدي وقت للاستماع إلى محاضرتك
Just get to the point.
قل مباشرة النقطة الرئيسية
I know Taiyu Group has been trying
أعرف أن مجموعة تاي يو
to break into the Chinese market.
يريد دائما فتح السوق الصيني
For the past 2 years...
في السنوات الماضية
But honestly,
لكن
I don't trust you.
أنا حقا لا أصدقكم
We've already signed a preliminary agreement
لقد وقعنا
with Huaze Group.
‫مع مجموعة هوا تسه
As for you,
بالنسبة لك
I can offer a discounted service fee on that basis.
يمكنني تخفيض رسوم الخدمة على أساس هذا
Time's up.
انتهى خمس دقائق
Sorry.
عفوا
That's it.
هكذا
I
أنا
won't let Leader Group
لن أدعكم مجموعة لي ده
become the PR firm for our project.
أن تصبحوا شركة العلاقات العامة لمشروعنا
This decision is final.
لن يتغير هذا الأمر بعد الآن
I hope you enjoy your trip.
أتمنى أن تكون رحلتكم سعيدة
Stay a few more days in Capital City.
للعب في المدينة الرئيسية لبضعة أيام
Buy some skin care products.
لشراء بعض منتجات العناية بالبشرة
What a waste of time.
يا له من مضيعة للوقت
Let's go.
اذهب بسرعة
Stupid.
أيها الوغد
No respect at all.
بدون احترام
This is the most rude person I've ever met in my career.
هذا هو أكثر شخص وقح التقيت به منذ العمل
From start to finish, he never had any intention of negotiating with us.
لم يفكر أبداً في التحدث معنا
He agreed
وعدنا أن نأتي
to meet us
وافق على مقابلتنا
just to humiliate us.
من أجل إهانتنا
The more he acts like this,
كلما كان هكذا
the more determined I am to get this deal.
كلما أردت الحصول على هذه القضية
How do we do that?
كيف؟
We go to the hotel first.
إلى الفندق
I'll report to J.
‫اذهب للإبلاغ عن تشان أولا‬
Yao gave me five minutes,
أعطاني ياو تشي خمس دقائق
but he interrupted me 3 times while I was speaking.
لكن قطعت شرحي ثلاث مرات متتالية
This isn't a negotiation.
هذا ليس التفاوض على الإطلاق
It's just him messing with us.
إنه يلعب بنا
Do you think it's impossible?
هل تعتقد أنه مستحيل؟
I just checked.
لقد تحققت للتو
In the past year,
في السنة الماضية
he's used a PR firm called Kangnai
ثلاث شركات أجنبية
for three of his overseas projects.
يستخدم شركة العلاقات العامة تدعى كانيا
The head of it is his cousin.
الشخص المسؤول هو ابن عمه
So I believe this time,
لذلك أعتقد هذه المرة
he'll probably hand the project
أنه قد يضع المشروع
to a PR firm
في الشركة العلاقات العامة
he can fully control.
في شركة العلاقات العامة
We might have come all the way here for nothing.
قد نذهب هباءً
Zhao.
تشاو
We need to get Yao Youzhi no matter the cost.
يجب أن نقبض على ياو يو جي بأي ثمن
But the usual negotiation tactics
لكن الآن طريقة التفاوض العادية
won't work.
لا فائدة على الإطلاق
So we'll use unconventional methods.
إذًا استخدم الطريقة المميزة
Listen up.
اسمع جيدا
By any means necessary.
لا تتردد بأي ثمن
Leader Group must become
يجب أن تكون مجموعة لي ده
the only PR firm for the nuclear power project.
شركة العلاقات العامة الوحيدة
This won't be easy.
هذا الأمر صعب جدا
So I have to ask.
لذلك أريد أن أسألك
Is this cooperation
هل هذا التعاون
related to our larger plan?
هل له علاقة بخطتنا الكبيرة
It's the boss's order.
هذا أمر الرئيس
You know the stakes.
أنت تفهم
Alright, I got it.
حسنًا فهمت
Zhao.
تشاو
I trust you.
أنا أثق بك
Has J ever said
قال تشان أنه لا يتردد بأي ثمن
“by any means necessary” before?
هل سمعتم ما قاله من قبل؟
No.
لا
Actually, I don't get it.
في الواقع أنا لا أفهم
This is just a regular nuclear power project.
هذا مجرد تعاون الكهرباء العادي
The technology is top-notch,
على الرغم من أن التكنولوجيا أفضل
but it doesn't seem worth him giving it this much attention.
لكن لا يستحق اهتمامه كثيرا
Do you know why?
هل تعرفون لماذا
How did he talk to us?
كيف قال لنا
He's a sly old fox.
إنه ثعلب عجوز
Besides, it doesn't matter whether he said it or not.
لا يهم إذا قلت أم لا
The key is that we need to take action.
المهم أنه يجب أن نتحرك
We need a plan,
يجب أن يكون لدينا خطة
and we need to
ماذا يجب أن نفعل؟
move forward.
‫أريد الحركة‬
What do you think?
هل لديك فكرة
Let's do this the hard way.
بقوة
He's already been tough with us,
إنه قوي جدا
so what's the next step?
كيف يجب أن يكون قاسيًا؟
Have you noticed the relationship
هل لاحظتم
between him and his secretary?
العلاقة بينه وبين سكرتيره
I noticed it right away.
لقد اكتشفت منذ وقت طويل
His secretary has a nice figure.
إن سكرتيرته جميلة
Yao Youzhi was staring at her lecherously。
ياو يو جي تنظر إليها بصمت
They
العلاقة بينهما
seem to have a special bond.
بالتأكيد ليست عادية
Let's dig deeper,
دعنا نحقق في الأمر
and see if we can gather some evidence.
للحصول على الدليل في أقرب وقت ممكن
That's a good idea. I'm on board.
بالتأكيد طريقة جيدة أنا موافق
But it's not going to be easy.
لكن بالتأكيد ليس سهلا
This is his turf.
هذه منطقته
You can do whatever you want?
ماذا تريد
I'll go contact our informant
سأتواصل مع مخبرينا أولا
and see what we can dig up.
لنرى ما يمكن العثور عليه
Miss.
آنستي
Here's the proof of Yao Youzhi
هذا هو الدليل
bribing executives and cohabiting with his subordinate.
دليل على رشوة القادة والموظفين
You were right.
أنت على حق
They're having an affair.
العلاقة بينهما غير طبيعية
While these pieces of evidence
هذه الأدلة
will have some impact when exposed,
على الرغم من أنه سيؤثر على ذلك
I feel like it's still not enough.
لكنني أشعر دائمًا أنه ليس مباشرًا بما فيه الكفاية
The bribe could be explained as a loan,
الرشوة يمكن القول أنها اقتراض المال
and the photos of his secretary
هذه الصور للمسكرتيرة
could be passed off as part of her job.
يمكنه استخدام العمل كعذر تمامًا
We need to go directly to his house
إذاً اذهب إلى منزله مباشرة
and find the most direct evidence.
للبحث عن الأدلة المباشرة
It'd be best if we could capture something explosive,
من الأفضل أن تصور
either on video or through photos.
أو تسجيل شيء رائع
Good, good, good.
حسنا حسنا
This is my favorite game.
هذه هي اللعبة المفضلة لدي
Yang Guang.
يانغ جوانج
Hi.
مرحباً
What kind of expression is that?
ما تعبيرك
Surprise, or shock?
مفاجأة أم مفاجأة
Wait a minute.
انتظر لحظة
You really came.
أنت هنا حقًا
You extended the invitation,
دعوتك
so I couldn't refuse.
أنا غير مهذب
Let me introduce.
دعني أقدم لك
These two are my colleagues.
هذان زملائي
This is my good friend Yang Guang from Yanping.
هذه صديقتي في يان بينغ يانغ قوانغ
Hi.
مرحباً
I'm Taylor from the International Business Department of Leader Group.
أنا تايلور من قسم الأعمال الدولية لمجموعة ليد
Nice to meet you.
سررت بلقائك
Your Chinese is very good.
‫أحسنت اللغة الصينية
I'm Li Taiheng, Vice Minister from the International Business Department.
نائب مدير قسم الأعمال الدولية لي تاي هنغ
Nice to meet you.
سررت بلقائك
I'm Yang Guang.
يانغ قوانغ
General Manager of Yanping Chaoyang Trading Company.
‫يان بينغ المدير العام لشركة تشاو يانغ التجارية
Nice to meet you.
سررت بلقائكم
Alright, you two go ahead.
اذن اصعدوا أولا
After his check-in,
بعد أن أنتهي من الإقامة معه
we can continue talking.
سنواصل الحديث
Okay.
حسنا
Let's give them some space.
دعنا نترك لهم بعض المساحة
Just joking.
هل تمزح؟
These two are pretty funny.
إنهما مضحكان جدا
Hi,
‫مرحبا‬
please give him a room on the seventh floor.
أعطه غرفة في الطابق السابع.
And bill it together with room 0721
سندفع الحساب مع غرفة 0721.
under the Leader Group.
سجلها تحت مجموعة ليد
Okay, one moment, please.
حسنا انتظر قليلا
Wait.
اتفقنا
I'll pay for the room myself.
سأدفع الفاتورة بنفسي
Okay.
حسنا
This time, I'm not taking care of anything.
لا أهتم بأي شيء هذه المرة
Please.
هذا
Yes, please.
نعم هذا
Okay.
حسنا
Here's your room card. Enjoy your stay.
إليك بطاقة الغرفة، أتمنى لك رحلة سعيدة
Thank you.
شكرا
Let's go.
لنذهب
Mr. Yang is cautious.
السيد يانغ حذر
Mr. Yang doesn't want to write a self-reflection.
السيد يانغ الذي لا يريد كتابة النقد الذاتي
Left.
يسار
Okay.
حسناً
Come in.
تفضل بالدخول
I thought your boss wouldn't agree
اعتقدت أن رئيسكم
to let you take time off.
لن يوافق على طلب إجازة
How about your colleagues?
ماذا عن زملائك؟
They've gone back to Yanping.
لقد عادوا إلى يان بينغ
The room is quite large.
الغرفة كبيرة جدا
Yeah.
نعم
At the Capital City Hotel,
في فندق شوتشنغ
there aren't many rooms with this much space.
لا يوجد الكثير من الغرف الكبيرة
It's very convenient.
إنه مريح جدا في الأسفل
Lots of restaurants downstairs.
الكثير من المطاعم
Pretty good.
جيد جدا
New development.
هناك تقدم
Sorry.
آسف
I still have some work to finish.
لدي بعض الأعمال لم أنهيها
I'll join you for dinner
بعد 40 دقيقة
in about 40 minutes.
سأتناول العشاء معك
No problem, you go ahead.
لا مشكلة، لا تقلقي
See you later.
أراك لاحقا
Goodbye.
مع السلامة
Alright.
هكذا
I'll send you my hotel address.
سأرسل لك عنواني
Once you're done on your end,
بعد الانتهاء من عملك
you can move over here.
يمكنك الانتقال إلى فندقي
I've got something to take care of now.
لدي بعض الأمور
Talk later. Bye.
سأذهب للعمل مع السلامة
[The Capital City Hotel's Location]
موقع فندق شو تشينج
Hello?
‫ألو‬
Hello, Director Zhang.
‫ألو المدير تشانغ‬
They've invited me
‫أرسل لي دعوة‬
to stay a few more days in Capital City.
طلب مني البقاء في العاصمة لبضعة أيام
This is a great opportunity for us to get close to them.
هذه فرصة جيدة للتواصل معهم قريبًا
Alright,
حسناً
then let's go along with it.
إذاً سنستخدم الخدعة
I'll apply for special approval for you
سأتقدم بطلب من الرؤساء
to stay in Capital City.
أن تبقي في المدينة الرئيسية
Ms. Zhao.
المدير تشاو
There's new progress?
هناك تقدم جديد
The villa location has been confirmed.
تم تحديد موقع الفيلا
It's at the Guangya Villa.
الحي السكني في فيلا قوانغ يا
Security measures are very strict.
الإجراءات الأمنية صارمة للغاية
Non-owners have to go through
إذا أراد المالك الدخول
detailed registration to enter.
يجب أن يتم التسجيل بالتفصيل
Yao Youzhi lives in No.13,
ياو يو جي يعيش في المبنى الثالث عشر
and the owner's registration is under his younger brother's name.
تسجيل المالك هو شقيقه الصغير
Okay, I'll investigate the villa situation.
حسناً سأكتشف الوضع في الفيلا
You focus on getting his schedule for these days.
أنتم مسؤولون عن الحصول على جدوله هذه الأيام
We'll work separately.
لنتحرك بشكل منفصل
Okay.
حسنا
Don't worry.
لا تقلق
J.
تشان
I heard Yang Guang went to see you.
سمعت أن يانغ قوانغ ذهب إليك
They report back pretty quickly.
لقد أبلغا في الوقت المناسب
After Yang Guang finished his work,
بعد انتهاء عمل يانغ قوانغ
he asked for leave and came over.
بعد انتهاء العمل
Good.
جيد
We must take advantage of this opportunity.
هذه المرة يجب أن نستغل الفرصة للقبض عليه
This is a rare chance.
فرصة نادرة
Honestly,
بصراحة
the incident before we came to Capital City
ما حدث قبل أن آتي إلى العاصمة
was really awkward.
كان محرجًا حقًا
I don't feel very confident about it.
‫ليس لدي ثقة كبيرة‬
You have to trust your charm.
يجب أن تصدقي سحرك
I think that
أعتقد
as long as he came to see you,
طالما يأتي إليك
it means he has a deep liking for you.
هذا يعني أنه يحبك كثيرا
As for what you said,
أما ما قلته
I think he's already understood and forgiven you.
أعتقد أنه يفهمك ويسامحك
Maybe.
ربما
But this kind of negotiation,
لكن هذه اللعبة
whether it succeeds or not,
سواء نجحت أم لا
depends on who can stay calm,
يجب أن نرى من يستطيع الصبر أكثر
doesn't it?
أليس كذلك
You can decide the pace.
أنت تقرر أي إيقاع
But I think
لكن أعتقد
if we can win him over in Capital City,
إن استطعت القبض عليه في المدينة الرئيسية هذه المرة
once we return to Yanping,
العودة إلى يان بينغ
we'll be able to ask him for help.
يمكننا أن نطلب منه المساعدة
Like strengthening relations
على سبيل المثال
with Huaze Group.
‫مع مجموعة هوا تسه
Alright, I'll give it a try.
حسنا سأحاول
Of course,
بالطبع
you still need to stay alert.
يجب أن تكون حذراً
After all, his position is special.
بعد كل شيء هويته خاصة
You can't be too careless.
لا يمكن أن ينقص الدفاع
I understand.
فهمت
Alright.
حسناً
I believe in your abilities.
أنا أثق بقدرتك
I look forward to your success.
سأنتظر عودتك
Alright.
حسناً
Hi.
مرحباً
Wow.
آه
You wear so formal
لنأكل
for the dinner.
أنتِ مهمة جداً
Is my outfit
هل ملابسي
not a bit mismatched with yours?
لا يناسبك
Before we eat, come with me to a place.
رافقني إلى مكان ما قبل تناول الطعام
Where?
إلى أين
Guangya Villa.
فيلا قوانغ يا
Dining in a villa?
تناول الطعام في الفيلا
How fancy.
رائع
I really like Capital City.
أحب المدينة
So I'm thinking of buying a house here.
لذا أريد أن أبني هنا
Li Taiheng recommended
لقد رشح لي تاي هنغ لي
Guangya Villa to me.
فيلا قوانغ يا
I'd like you to accompany me for a visit.
أريدك أن ترافقني للتحقق
I think right now,
أعتقد في هذا الوقت
investments should be cautious.
الاستثمار يحتاج إلى الحذر
It's better to keep the money in your own hands for now.
من الأفضل أن تمسك بالمال في يديك
Okay.
حسنا
Can you drive?
هل يمكنك القيادة
Yes.
نعم
Let's go.
هيا
Hello, J.
تشان ماذا حدث
Who are you with?
مع من أنت؟
Li Taiheng.
أنا ولي تاي هنغ
Do you want to find Zhao?
هل تحتاج إلى تشاو؟
No.
لا
This matter,
هذا الأمر
only the two of you
فقط أنتما الاثنان تعرفان
need to know.
يكفي
Alright.
حسنا
Go ahead.
تكلم
You need to closely monitor
كن حذراً
Zhao
تشاو و يانغ جوانج
and Yang Guang,
الوضع بينهما
especially Yang Guang.
خاصة يانغ جوانج
You mean, you don't trust Yang Guang?
هل تقصد أنك لا تثق بـ يانغ قوانغ
You don't know.
أنتم لا تعرفون
He's an agent from State Security.
إنه عميل خاص لجوه آن
His identity
هويته
is too special.
مميز جدا
So we have to prevent him from
لذلك علينا منعه
having any personal plans or ideas.
أي خطط أو أفكاره الخاصة
If he's playing a part,
إذا كان يمثل
any suspicious move would mean
إذا كان هناك أي تحركات مريبة
that the Chinese Ministry of State Security
هذا يعني أن قسم الأمن الوطني
has already targeted Leader Group.
قد راقب لي ده
And we'll need to figure out how to deal with it.
يجب أن نجد طريقة للتعامل معها
If necessary,
حتى في الوقت الضروري
we can eliminate him.
‫يمكنك حله‬
We can make him disappear.
يمكن أن تجعله مفقود
In a foreign country,
في دولة أجنبية
it'll be harder for them to investigate.
من الصعب أن يكتشفوا شيئاً
Anyway,
على أي حال
we cannot let anyone
لا تدع أي شخص
affect our plans.
يؤثر على خطتنا
Got it.
فهمت
We'll keep an eye on them, don't worry.
سنراقبه اطمئن
That's it.
هكذا
From now on,
‫من الآن فصاعداً
you're my fiancé.
‫أنت خطيبي
This will help me bargain.
‫ساعديني، هذا سهل
Don't talk too much later.
لا تتحدث كثيرا بعد قليل
Are you interested in Guangya Villa?
أنتما تريدان شراء فيلا قوانغ يا
Great choice.
لديك ذوق جيد
This is one of the most luxurious
هذا أفضل
villa areas in the Capital City.
في المدينة
But the price is also very expensive...
لكن سعر المنزل غالي جدا
Price is not an issue.
السعر ليس مشكلة
Got it.
فهمت
By the way,
بالمناسبة
I studied in China before.
لقد درست في الصين من قبل
You can speak Chinese.
يمكنك أن تخبرني باللغة الصينية
We're in a rush.
نحن في عجلة من أمرنا
Do you have any available house?
هل لديك شقة
We want to see the houses first.
نريد أن نرى الشقة أولا
Of course.
بالطبع لا
Hello.
مرحبا
Are you the resident here?
هل هو المالك
Hey, excuse me.
مرحباً شكراً لك
I'm the agent from Rich Real Estate.
أنا وكيلة شركة فوجوي العقارية
And they're the visitors for buying the property here.
إنهم هنا لشراء المنزل
I'm pretty close with your boss.
أنا أعرف مدير شركتكم
Okay, please hurry up.
من فضلك أسرع
Thanks a lot.
شكرا
In this noisy era,
في هذا العصر الصخب
the exterior of buildings can be cloned,
مظهره المبنى يمكن أن يكون عظيما
but only the environment of the building,
فقط بيئة البناء
just like your two temperaments,
مثل مزاجكما
is unique.
فريد
The Guangya Villa
أين فيلا قوانغ يا
is located...
في
What kind of people live here?
من هم المالك هنا
You're asking the right person.
لقد سألت
These are all well-known figures,
جميعها مشهورة هنا
some are even celebrities.
هناك بعض النجوم
Superstar.
النجمة الكبيرة
The environment here is not bad, right?
هل البيئة هنا جيدة
Which direction is north?
أي اتجاه هو الشمال
It's this way.
هنا
It is not north?
أين الشمال
This is south.
هذا جنوب
Fine.
تشونغ
Let me introduce it to you.
دعني أقدم لكم
This is No.11,
هنا 11
12,
واحد اثنان
all the way to No.19.
إلى المبنى 19
This side is from No. 21 to 29.
‫من هنا رقم‪21 ‬إلى‪29 ‬‬
The ones ahead
ماذا عن الأمام؟
are No. 31 to 39.
رقم 31 إلى 39
Let's walk this way.
‫دعنا نذهب بهذا الطريق‬
Of course.
بالطبع لا
Please.
تفضل
Every road is connected
ماذا عن فيلا قوانغ يا
in the Guangya Villa.
كل طريق متصلة
It's very convenient.
‫مريح جدا‬
This is No.12.
‫من هنا رقم‪12 ‬‬
That's No.13.
هنا رقم 13
Each villa complements each other,
كل فيلا تتبادل
but also
وفي نفس الوقت
has its own unique style.
هناك أسلوب مختلف
The greenery you see now
ما تراه الآن
was designed by a German designer,
تم دعوة المصممين الألماني
Stefan.
تصميم ستيفين
Look at this tree, its shape
انظر إلى هذه الشجرة مثيرة للاهتمام
is quite interesting.
شكلها الخارجي
It has been around for about 15 years.
حوالي 15 عامًا
So,
لذلك
villas of this standard
الفيلا مثل هذا
are truly rare to come by.
لا يمكن الحصول عليها
I know the price...
أعرف هذا السعر
I'll buy it.
أنا متأكد من ذلك
Full payment.
كامل
The transfer has a limit.
محدود للحويل
Tomorrow,
غدا
I'll bring a check to the store to find you.
سآخذ الشيكة للبحث عنك في المتجر
Ms. Zhao,
سيدة تشاو
thank you so much.
شكرا جزيلا
Thank you.
شكرا
Thank you, thank you very much.
شكرا جزيلا جزيلا
Can you pay the deposit today?
هل يمكنك دفع الوديعة اليوم
No problem.
لا مشكلة
Then please follow me.
تعال معي من فضلك
You go ahead.
عودي أولا
I'll walk around with my husband.
أريد أن أتجول مع زوجي في الحي
We want to
للاستمتاع
feel the atmosphere here.
الجو في هذا الحي
We can also plan for
من الجيد التخطيط
future renovation and decoration.
خطة التغيير والتصميم في المستقبل
Right?
صحيح
Yes.
نعم
I'll leave you two.
لن أزعجكما
Enjoy.
استمتعا
Really buying?
اشتريها حقا
Who's buying?
من يشتري
Didn't you say we need to keep the money in our hands?
ألم تقل أنك تريد وضع المال في يدك
I just want to walk around the community.
أريد فقط التجول في الحي
Hey, Long. Okay. I got it. I'll be right there.
"لونغ"، فهمت، سأذهب الآن.
What are the clients?
ماذا عن الضيوف؟
They just wonder to take a bit more time to look around.
إنهم يريدون أن يشعروا بالمحديقة مرة أخرى
I'm not sure that's really appropriate.
هذا غير مناسب
Why not?
لماذا غير مناسب
They've already decided to buy.
لقد قرروا شرائها
And they'll gonna be the owners.
سيكون مالكك في المستقبل
Don't disturb them. You know, it won't help you.
لا تزعجهم هذا ليس جيدا لك
They're my clients, just trust me.
عميلي الذي أحضرته اطمئن
Thanks a lot.
شكرا
It seems like we've circled back around.
يبدو أننا عدنا مرة أخرى
We were just walking up from below.
لقد ذهبنا للتو من الأسفل للأعلى
Wait for me.
انتظرني
Let's go.
لنذهب
Is No.13 villa
فيلا رقم 13
your friend's house?
منزل صديقك
You seem especially interested in this villa.
يبدو أنك مهتم جداً بهذا الفيلا
When we just passed here,
فقط عندما مررت من هنا
you took out your phone
أخرجي هاتفك
and recorded a video.
وتسجيل الفيديو
Sorry, I didn't mean anything.
عفوا لا أقصد أي شيء آخر
It's just a professional habit.
أنا فقط مريضة المهنية
I couldn't help but say something when I saw it.
لم أتحمل أن أقول ما تراه
I don't need you to answer me,
لا أريدك أن تجيبني
but I also want to remind you,
لكن أريد أن أذكرك
don't do anything illegal.
لا تفعلي أشياء غير قانونية
This is the home of Mr. Yao Youzhi, the president of Taiyu Group.
هذا منزل رئيس مجموعة تاي يو ياو يو جي
Our initial negotiations
تفاوضنا الأولي
failed.
قد فشلت
Li Taiheng and the others
لي تاي هنغ والآخرين
are preparing new plans.
ليستعد خطة جديدة
I came here
أنا هنا
just in case.
من أجل الاحتياط
If necessary,
إذا كان الأمر ضروريًا
I'll have to block him at his house.
يجب أن آتي إلى المنزل لإيقافه
Then you could've just told me.
يمكنك أن تخبرني مباشرة
Didn't you already figure it out?
ألم تلاحظ ذلك إذا لم أقل؟
Don't flatter me.
لا تدفعني
I'm starving.
أنا جائع
I'll treat you to the most authentic food.
سأدعوك لتناول الطعام الأصلي
How authentic?
كم هو أصلي
You'll know once you try it.
ستعرف بعد أن تأكل
Hello, Minister Li.
ألو سيد لي
I'm having dinner with Mr. Yang.
أنا أتناول الطعام مع المدير يانغ
Sorry.
آسف
Let me tell you.
دعني أخبرك
About Yao Youzhi's schedule,
بشأن جدول ياو يو جي
I've tried everything,
أنا
but I still can't find anything.
لقد استخدمت الكثير من الطرق ولم أستطع معرفة ذلك
His schedule is extremely secret.
جدوله غامض للغاية
There's no info from the outside.
لا يوجد أي أخبار في الخارج
Do you know who has it?
هل تعرف من يعرف جدوله
The secretary's office of the CEO.
مكتب سكرتير مكتب الرئيس
They'd definitely know
جدول رئيسهم
their own boss's schedule.
لا بد أنهم يعرفون ذلك
I've tried reaching out to them,
لقد بحثت عنهم
but I haven't been able to get it.
لكنني لم أتمكن من التعامل معها
I'm worried it'll delay things,
أخشى أن أتأخر
so I had to let you know.
لذلك يجب أن أخبرك
I'll think about it.
سأفكر مرة أخرى
Alright.
حسنا
What's wrong?
ماذا حدث
You looked worried
بعد غلق الهاتف
right after the call.
تبدين حزينة
We've been trying to find out
كنا نستفسر
Yao Youzhi's schedule,
عن رحلة ياو يو جي
hoping to set up another meeting.
أريد مقابلته مرة أخرى
But we've
لكن الآن لا يمكنني الحصول على
got nothing so far.
معلومات جدوله
Haste makes waste.
إن كان سريعاً فلن يصل
You don't need to rush so much.
لا تقلقي
Eat first.
لنأكل أولا
When you're hungry,
السماء واسعة الأرض
nothing else matters.
معدتي أكبر
Can you do me a favor?
هل يمكنك مساعدتي؟
So, do you have an appointment with President Yao?
هل لديكم موعد للسيد ياو
No, I don't.
لا لا
But I'm hoping to do an interview with President Yao.
لكن آمل أن أستطيع مقابلة الرئيس ياو
My name is Casey Moore.
أنا كيس مول
And I'm with the Financial Times.
أنا صحفية في صحيفة المالية
Is he available right now?
هل لديه وقت الآن
I'm sorry.
عفوا
President Yao has been very busy recently.
الرئيس ياو مشغول مؤخراً
We need his approval before we can schedule an interview.
نحتاج موافقته
Okay, I know.
أعرف هذا
So could you please call him now
هل يمكنك الاتصال
to check?
للتأكد من ذلك
Well, to be honest, I'm not familiar with you.
بصراحة أنا لست على دراية بك
And I've never heard of your name before.
لم أسمعك من قبل
Hi,
مرحبا
what's your name?
ما اسمك
Chloe.
كري
Hi, Chloe, nice to meet you.
كري سررت بلقائك
Nice to meet you.
سررت بلقائك
You can call me Tom Jerry.
يمكنك مناداتي تون جيري
Hi, Jerry.
مرحباً جيري
Hey, listen.
‫هكذا
This is an urgent task.
لأن هذه مهمة عاجلة
And for this interview,
هذه المقابلة
I want to talk about
أريد أن أتحدث عن الأخبار
the recent rumors about the sanction against Taiyu Group.
سيعاقب مجموعة تاي يو
You know.
هل تعرف
Our Finance Times
صحيفة المالية خاصتنا
is a highly influential media.
وسائل الإعلام ذات تأثير كبير
And our reports
إن تقريرنا
can impact your group's future.
له تأثير مهم على تطوير المستقبل
I really hope
آمل حقا
we can clear up any misunderstandings as soon as possible.
أن نتخلص من سوء الفهم في أقرب وقت ممكن
So,
لذلك
I think you should take my proposal seriously.
أعتقد أنك يجب أن تهتم برأيي
So may I see your press cards, please?
هل يمكنني إلقاء نظرة على بطاقتك؟
Oh, sure.
بالطبع
And yours?
ماذا عنك؟
If you don't trust us,
إذا لم تثق بنا
then we'll
سنعطيكم
respond accordingly.
الأخبار التي لا تثق بها
I think you'd better understand the result of this.
يجب أن تعرف عواقب هذا الأمر
You know what I mean？
مفهوم؟
Hold on, please.
انتظر لحظة
Thanks a lot.
شكرا
So he's not available tomorrow.
ليس لدى الرئيس وقت غدًا
How about the day after tomorrow at 3 pm here in the meeting room?
في غرفة الاجتماعات في الساعة الثالثة بعد غد ممكن
Great.
حسنا
Thank you, appreciate it.
شكرا شكرا جزيلا
Thank you.
شكرا
Have a nice day.
حياة سعيدة
You too.
أنت أيضا
Turn on your Bluetooth.
افتح الهاتف الأزرق
Okay.
حسنا
You're really good at this.
قدرة العمل قوية جدا
So are you.
أنت أيضا
Tom Jerry, Casey Moore.
تونم جيري كيس مول
Which one do you like?
هل تحبين ذلك
Tom or...
هل توم
Alright, it's sent.
حسنًا انتهيت
Good.
حسناً
Tomorrow morning, he'll be at the golf course.
سيذهب إلى الملعب الجولف صباح الغد
That should be an opportunity.
يجب أن تكون فرصة
I'll meet him.
سأذهب لمقابلته
Okay.
حسنا
From here on, it's your turn.
التالي هو عملك
Excuse me.
مرحبا
I want to take this.
غلقها
Okay.
حسنا
Thank you so much.
شكرا
What did you buy?
ماذا اشتريت؟
It's for you.
هذا لك
Thank you.
شكرا
It's pretty special.
إنه مميز جدا
It's not something expensive.
ليس شيء ثمين
But, like you said,
لكن كما قلت
it's pretty special.
مميز جدا
Have you seen my department's logo?
هل رأيت علامة شركتنا من قبل
No.
لا
How could I have seen it?
كيف رأيت ذلك
Sword, shield, Great Wall, pine branches.
ورقة سيف حادة
The sword is hidden behind the shield,
السيف مخبأة خلف القناة
only the hilt and the tip of the sword are visible.
أظهر فقط مقبض السيف والปลาย السيف
Doesn't that seem quite similar?
هل هو متشابه؟
So what does this mean?
ماذا يعني هذا؟
The sword is hidden in the shield,
السيف مخبأة في الدفاع
shown only by the shield,
لإظهار الدفاع
and the sharp edge warns the enemy.
ضد العدو
If the shield fails,
إذا فشلت الدفاع
the sword will strike,
سيف حاد
slaying the enemy and protecting our land.
اقتلوا الأعداء وحماية جبل النهر
I didn't know
لا أعرف
it had so much meaning.
أن هناك الكثير من المعنى
So why are you giving me this?
لماذا تعطيني هذا
To protect your safety.
لحمايتك
I wish you always walk on the right path.
أتمنى أن تسير في الطريق الصحيح
Is it in your role as Division Director Yang
بصفتك المدير يانغ
or Sonny?
أو ساني
Tom Jerry.
تون جيري
Help me put it on.
ساعدني في ارتدائها
Okay.
حسنا
Thank you, I really like it.
شكرًا، أعجبني كثيرًا
No problem.
على الرحب والسعة
Tired?
هل أنت متعب؟
Not really.
لا بأس
After having an ice cream cone, I woke up.
استيقظت بعد تناول علبة حلوى
Want to climb a hill?
‫لا تتعب اذهب لتسلق الجبل‬
What?
ماذا؟
There's a mountain in Capital City.
هناك جبل
We can see the city's night view from it.
في المدينة
Okay, go.
حسنا لنذهب
Go.
هيا
I'll take this call.
أجب على الهاتف
Hello?
ألو
Yang Guang is with you, right?
هل يانغ قوانغ معك
Yes.
نعم
When will you be back?
متى ستعود
We still need to discuss
يجب أن نناقش
the next steps.
الخطة التالية
About an hour.
تبقى أكثر من ساعة
Will that be fine?
هل لدينا الوقت؟
That'll be fine, no problem.
لا مشكلة
We'll wait for you.
سأنتظرك
If you're busy,
إذا كنت مشغولا
just go back.
عودي أولا
We'll climb another day.
سنتسلق في يوم آخر
It's fine.
لا بأس
We're here already,
لقد وصلنا إلى هنا
it'd be a shame not to go up.
من المؤسف ألا تصعد
Okay.
حسنا
Let's make a bet.
دعنا نراهن
Whoever gets to the top first wins.
من يصل إلى قمة الجبل أولاً سيفوز
The winner can
الشخص الفائز
ask the other person
يمكن أن
a question.
عن شخص آخر
Isn't that childish?
هل أنت ساذج
What's the bet?
ماذا تراهنين
Dare to bet money?
هل تجرؤ على الرهان؟
Alright.
حسنا
Get ready, go.
استعدوا
The tortoise and the hare, huh?
مسابقة السلحفاة والأرنب
There's no problem with the sound.
الصوت بخير
Bingo.
انتهيت
Okay.
حسنا
Not bad.
جيد
You've been working out, huh?
لقد تدربت كثيراً
Of course.
بالطبع
You're not bad, Director Yang.
أنت جيد يا سيد يانغ
I almost couldn't catch up with the hare.
كدت أطارد الأرنب
Let's call it a draw.
نحن تعادل
We can each ask one question.
يمكن لكل شخص أن يأخذ واحدة
Alright.
حسنًا
Isn't it beautiful?
أليست جميلة؟
Yes.
نعم
It really is quite beautiful.
إنها جميلة حقًا
Go ahead, ask.
اسأل
I want to ask you,
أريد أن أسألك
you've always trusted me,
أنت دائما تصدقني
right?
أليس كذلك
I trust the facts.
أنا أؤمن بالحقيقة
I trust the evidence.
أثق بالأدلة
If the facts and evidence
إذا كان الحقيقة والأدلة
prove that you're a good person,
يثبت أنك شخص جيد
then why wouldn't I trust you?
لماذا لا أصدقك؟
If the facts and evidence
إذا كان الحقيقة والأدلة
don't prove,
لا يمكن إثبات ذلك
would you still trust me?
هل ستصدقني؟
That's another question.
هذا سؤال آخر
You broke the rules.
لقد انتهكت القواعد
Alright.
حسنا
Ask.
اسأل
If the facts and evidence
إذا كان الحقيقة والأدلة
don't prove,
لا يمكن إثبات ذلك
should I still trust you?
هل يجب أن أصدقك؟
I hope you can trust me.
أتمنى أن تصدقني
Yang Guang.
يانغ قوانغ
Photoshop it.
تعديل الصور
I'm really happy today.
أنا سعيدة اليوم
How about you?
وأنت
Quite relaxed.
استرخي
You're right.
أنت على حق
Sometimes taking a break,
في بعض الأحيان أعطي نفسك إجازة
I feel pretty good.
أنا في مزاج جيد
That's good.
هذا جيد
Thank you
شكرا لك
for helping me so much today.
لقد ساعدتني كثيرا اليوم
No problem.
على الرحب والسعة
Goodnight.
ليلة سعيدة
Where's my cup?
أين كوبي؟
So why are you giving me this?
لماذا تعطيني هذا؟
To protect your safety.
لحمايتك
I wish you always walk
أتمنى أن تمشي
on the right path.
في الطريق الصحيح
Electric motors for dump trucks manufactured by Geely-Tuo
المحرك الكهربائي الذي صنعه لي توه
are being produced at full speed.
‫في انتاج بسرعة
The most advanced electric motors in the world
‫أفضل حركة كهربائية في هذا العالم
will be installed between the rear wheels of the dump truck,
سيتم وضعه في
driving the rear wheels to rotate.
تدور العجلان الخلفية بين العجلان
This technology makes the operation of the dump truck
هذه التكنولوجيا
more reliable and powerful.
القيادة أكثر موثوقية وقوية
Such a boring man.
يا له من رجل ممل.
All he does when he comes back is watching TV.
لا تعرف سوى مشاهدة التلفزيون
But the world hasn't...
لكن لا يوجد أحد في العالم
Who's that?
من
It's me.
إنه أنا
Wait a minute.
انتظر
Hi.
مرحباً
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل
Waiting for you.
أنتظرك
Waiting for you to discuss
ننتظرك لنبحث معا
the next steps.
الخطة التالية
What's that sound?
ما هذا الصوت
It's the phone.
الهاتف
The sound of the phone ringing.
صوت الهاتف
Tomorrow morning,
صباح الغد
Yao Youzhi will be at the golf course,
سيذهب ياو يو جي إلى الملعب الجولف
playing with the Deputy Minister of Electricity.
للعب مع نائب وزير الكهرباء
I need to know his whereabouts at all times.
أحتاج إلى معرفة مكان وجوده في أي وقت
You two are responsible for following him.
أنتما الاثنان مسؤولان عن متابعته
Then you're in charge of installing the equipment.
أنت مسؤول عن الترتيب
I'll go.
سأذهب
Today, I've been to the Guangya Villa,
ذهبت إلى فيلا قوانغ يا اليوم
and I've already checked the security and environment of the community.
لقد عرفت الأمن والبيئة في الحي
Good.
حسنا
Then let's keep a close eye on him tomorrow.
سنراقبه غدا